SASCHA ANDEWEG

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / LINGUISTIC MODELER

EDUCATION

1985-1988

LEAVING CERT

Zwin College, Oostburg, The Netherlands

198

TYPING

1988-1990

BASIC PREPRESS

GOC. Rotterdam. The Netherlands

1990-1991

GRAPHIC TECHNICIAN PREPRESS

GOC, Rotterdam, The Netherlands

1998

BASIC WEBDESIGN AND HTML

GOC The Netherlands

1999

DREAMWEAVER/FLASH COURSE

GOC The Netherlands

2010

TRAINING 'EXPERT IN SALES'

Kenneth Smit, The Netherlands

2011

WORKSHOP COLUMN WRITING

 $\hbox{Marjon Sarneel, The Netherlands}$

2019

FULL STACK WEBDEVELOPER

CodeInstitute, Dublin, Ireland

SKILLS

Indesign

Photoshop

Illustrator

Webdesign

Webdevelopment

EXPERIENCE

2016 - Present

GLOBETECH LTD.

Linguistic Grader/Modeler

Linguistic analysis for machine learning and artificial intelligence. Due to a non-disclosure contract I cannot share further detail about the position.

1985 - 2016

DRUKKERIJ BAREMAN / TEKSTBEELD GROEP

Prepress specialist

From the early days of phototype setting to digital printing and webdesign I have covered most of the disciplines you can think of in a medium sized printing company.

2006 - 2016

RAMMELOO COMMUNICATIONS

Graphic Designer

Outside office hours I did the layout of a local paper and a lot of presentation material.

STATEMENT

As a graphic designer for a medium sized company with a very wide variety of clients I learned to think outside the box of just being a graphic designer following orders. I contributed to marketing strategies, corporate styles, textual concepts, our own business decisions and so on. I'm confident that my experience can benefit your organization in various ways too.

CONTACT

20 Hawthorn Crescent Forest Glen, P61K253 Fermoy, Co. Cork T: 089 7028 790

E: sascha@designed.irish www.designed.irish (soon restyled)

SOCIAL MEDIA

 https://www.linkedin.com/in/ sascha-andeweg-6885aa117/

HOBBIES/INTERESTS

- Music
- Photography
- Graphic Design

REFERENCES

Emma Flynn

HR Manager Globetech Ltd.

T: 21 4839380

E: emma.flynn@globetech.ie

Adri Bareman

CEO TekstBeeld Groep T: +31 115 613072 E: a.bareman@tekstbeeld.nl

Ronny Rammeloo

Rammeloo Communications **T:** +31 117 453467 **E:** ryro@zeelandnet.nl